[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "Yet again I ask you, Ali, what the hell is going on?", "question_tokens": ["Yet", "again", "I", "ask", "you", ",", "Ali", ",", "what", "the", "hell", "is", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "You know, Piers, every day, I get up very early.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "every", "day", ",", "I", "get", "up", "very", "early", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ali"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Everyone has specter of Lehman Brothers hanging over them, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Everyone", "has", "specter", "of", "Lehman", "Brothers", "hanging", "over", "them", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Lehman Brothers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Societe Generale"], "PERCENT": ["15 percent"], "LOCATION": ["Europe"]}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Can we see the possibility somewhere in Europe or America of banks going under of the scale of Lehman Brothers?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "see", "the", "possibility", "somewhere", "in", "Europe", "or", "America", "of", "banks", "going", "under", "of", "the", "scale", "of", "Lehman", "Brothers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well, in fact, one of the triggers today was one of Europe's largest banks, Societe Generale, losing 15 percent.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "fact", ",", "one", "of", "the", "triggers", "today", "was", "one", "of", "Europe", "'s", "largest", "banks", ",", "Societe", "Generale", ",", "losing", "15", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Lehman Brothers"], "LOCATION": ["Europe", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Is it still a sensible place to put some money right now or is it now too expensive?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "still", "a", "sensible", "place", "to", "put", "some", "money", "right", "now", "or", "is", "it", "now", "too", "expensive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "When the lemmings start running towards that direction, what you want to do is run in the opposite direction.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "the", "lemmings", "start", "running", "towards", "that", "direction", ",", "what", "you", "want", "to", "do", "is", "run", "in", "the", "opposite", "direction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Where are we, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "we", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, double dips are actually very, very rare.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "double", "dips", "are", "actually", "very", ",", "very", "rare", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RBR", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "What advise -- if you were writing speeches right now for President Obama, what advice would you give him now to ramp up the rhetoric in an effective way?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advise", "--", "if", "you", "were", "writing", "speeches", "right", "now", "for", "President", "Obama", ",", "what", "advice", "would", "you", "give", "him", "now", "to", "ramp", "up", "the", "rhetoric", "in", "an", "effective", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "I think that it's worth recognizing first that this economic challenge is more than purely a rhetorical one.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "worth", "recognizing", "first", "that", "this", "economic", "challenge", "is", "more", "than", "purely", "a", "rhetorical", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "We need the president to reconnect with his voters really, don't we?", "question_tokens": ["We", "need", "the", "president", "to", "reconnect", "with", "his", "voters", "really", ",", "do", "n't", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "We do.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["France"]}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Who cares what happens in France?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "cares", "what", "happens", "in", "France", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, so let me tell you exactly what happened in France.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "so", "let", "me", "tell", "you", "exactly", "what", "happened", "in", "France", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["France"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Because that enables them to have growth.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "that", "enables", "them", "to", "have", "growth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "How is he going to get Americans back to work?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "he", "going", "to", "get", "Americans", "back", "to", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNPS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "I've said this before.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "said", "this", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Is this sensible or is that equally crazy?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "sensible", "or", "is", "that", "equally", "crazy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Well, it's just emotional which makes it crazy, because it doesn't get you where you want to go.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "emotional", "which", "makes", "it", "crazy", ",", "because", "it", "does", "n't", "get", "you", "where", "you", "want", "to", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Should people look to diversify into, you know, certainly more random investments?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "people", "look", "to", "diversify", "into", ",", "you", "know", ",", "certainly", "more", "random", "investments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNS", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Well, the collectibles category has never kept up with real estate or stock market category.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "collectibles", "category", "has", "never", "kept", "up", "with", "real", "estate", "or", "stock", "market", "category", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Because if you can't trust your bank, who can you trust?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "if", "you", "ca", "n't", "trust", "your", "bank", ",", "who", "can", "you", "trust", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Well, I agree.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Finally, Dave -- briefly if you don't mind -- is it ostrich time, in the sense that when these big things start exploding in this volatile way, is sometimes the best thing to do to stick your head straight in the sand and keep it there until it all blows over?", "question_tokens": ["Finally", ",", "Dave", "--", "briefly", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "mind", "--", "is", "it", "ostrich", "time", ",", "in", "the", "sense", "that", "when", "these", "big", "things", "start", "exploding", "in", "this", "volatile", "way", ",", "is", "sometimes", "the", "best", "thing", "to", "do", "to", "stick", "your", "head", "straight", "in", "the", "sand", "and", "keep", "it", "there", "until", "it", "all", "blows", "over", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "In a sense, that's true.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "a", "sense", ",", "that", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dave"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Or is that pride getting dented?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "that", "pride", "getting", "dented", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Well, I'm certainly proud to be an American.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "certainly", "proud", "to", "be", "an", "American", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Do you find yourself nodding when you hear her speak?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "find", "yourself", "nodding", "when", "you", "hear", "her", "speak", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Not her particularly.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "her", "particularly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Do you think the reputation of America is getting damaged badly in all this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "reputation", "of", "America", "is", "getting", "damaged", "badly", "in", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Yes, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Do you think that's right?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "I don't know they're the enemy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "they", "'re", "the", "enemy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Do you think more American business people should be doing that, should be looking more internally now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "more", "American", "business", "people", "should", "be", "doing", "that", ",", "should", "be", "looking", "more", "internally", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "I'm taking the hit.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "taking", "the", "hit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "To actually take a hit in the way you're describing is not really the American way, is it?", "question_tokens": ["To", "actually", "take", "a", "hit", "in", "the", "way", "you", "'re", "describing", "is", "not", "really", "the", "American", "way", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I don't know that it's the American way, but it's my way.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", "it", "'s", "the", "American", "way", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "my", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "What's the number one concern for them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "number", "one", "concern", "for", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "Paying their bills and keeping their job.", "answer_tokens": ["Paying", "their", "bills", "and", "keeping", "their", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "If you're the president, is that where you want to see the focus now, getting Americans back to work?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "the", "president", ",", "is", "that", "where", "you", "want", "to", "see", "the", "focus", "now", ",", "getting", "Americans", "back", "to", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Yeah, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Did you have to do that all year?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "to", "do", "that", "all", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "No, I didn't thankfully.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "thankfully", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Isn't he though?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "he", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "ORGAN: He is.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "He", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Of all of those things, what was the worst, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "of", "those", "things", ",", "what", "was", "the", "worst", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Well, my first divorce is not on there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "first", "divorce", "is", "not", "on", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "You mean your first divorce was worse than the second wife shooting you in the chest, was it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "mean", "your", "first", "divorce", "was", "worse", "than", "the", "second", "wife", "shooting", "you", "in", "the", "chest", ",", "was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "DKINS: It's easier to deal with somebody trying to kill you than somebody saying they don't love you anymore.", "answer_tokens": ["DKINS", ":", "It", "'s", "easier", "to", "deal", "with", "somebody", "trying", "to", "kill", "you", "than", "somebody", "saying", "they", "do", "n't", "love", "you", "anymore", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Did you think you were going to die?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "you", "were", "going", "to", "die", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Yeah, I do remember thinking that.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "do", "remember", "thinking", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Yeah, I've had some things happen to me that I didn't feel like I really deserve, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "'ve", "had", "some", "things", "happen", "to", "me", "that", "I", "did", "n't", "feel", "like", "I", "really", "deserve", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Your wife, who I had the pleasure of meeting a few times on \"Apprentice\" -- delightful lady.", "answer_tokens": ["Your", "wife", ",", "who", "I", "had", "the", "pleasure", "of", "meeting", "a", "few", "times", "on", "``", "Apprentice", "''", "--", "delightful", "lady", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", ":", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Is she well?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "She remembers you hitting on her when she was up at -- and that's cool.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "remembers", "you", "hitting", "on", "her", "when", "she", "was", "up", "at", "--", "and", "that", "'s", "cool", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Is that -- is that the nature of the beast?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "--", "is", "that", "the", "nature", "of", "the", "beast", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Yeah, it's part of the gig.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "it", "'s", "part", "of", "the", "gig", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Do you still feel that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "feel", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "You kind of got it all out of your system?", "question_tokens": ["You", "kind", "of", "got", "it", "all", "out", "of", "your", "system", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Does he still act as kind of a quiet motivating factor to you in your career, in your life?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "still", "act", "as", "kind", "of", "a", "quiet", "motivating", "factor", "to", "you", "in", "your", "career", ",", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "You know, I would like to be able to say yes, but I've moved now 17, 18 years past that.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "would", "like", "to", "be", "able", "to", "say", "yes", ",", "but", "I", "'ve", "moved", "now", "17", ",", "18", "years", "past", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "What would he have made of what's happened to you, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "he", "have", "made", "of", "what", "'s", "happened", "to", "you", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Oh, he'd be so proud.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "he", "'d", "be", "so", "proud", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110810pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "JJ", "VBZ", "NN", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Ali, I barely know how to ask you this, but have you got any idea what's going to happen in the markets tomorrow?", "question_tokens": ["Ali", ",", "I", "barely", "know", "how", "to", "ask", "you", "this", ",", "but", "have", "you", "got", "any", "idea", "what", "'s", "going", "to", "happen", "in", "the", "markets", "tomorrow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "I think what you should do before the markets open is pick up some Pepto-Bismol on your way in.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "what", "you", "should", "do", "before", "the", "markets", "open", "is", "pick", "up", "some", "Pepto-Bismol", "on", "your", "way", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]